

# Luca Vasile - Luca

O Home: Loc. Gheorghieni, Com. Feleacu, 407272, Cluj-Napoca, Romania

Email: <a href="mailto:vasilelucaluca@gmail.com">vasilelucaluca@gmail.com</a> Phone: (+40) 748794107

**Website:** <a href="https://luca-vasile-portfolio.netlify.app/">https://luca-vasile-portfolio.netlify.app/</a>

**Website:** <a href="https://github.com/vasiluca32?tab=repositories">https://github.com/vasiluca32?tab=repositories</a>

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/vasile-luca-luca

**Gender:** Male **Date of birth:** 30/01/1992 **Nationality:** Romanian

#### **ABOUT ME**

As a junior web developer at Tickbird, I have been working with the Angular framework for over a year, developing the company website and learning new tools along the way. I have a certificate from Udemy in The Complete Web Developer in 2022: Zero to Mastery, which demonstrates my commitment and passion for web development.

Before joining Tickbird, I gained valuable experience as a junior web developer at FrozenLogic, where I created reusable web modules that matched perfectly with the design, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Figma, Jira, Avocode and HubspotCMS. I worked in an agile team, delivering projects for clients from various sectors, such as agriculture, software, and finance. I enjoy solving problems, learning new things, and working collaboratively with others.

I discovered my passion for web development by completing the web development course at Informal School of IT in 2020 where I learned all the basics about front-end and got a taste about React which is curently my favorite stack.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

[27/08/2022 - 31/10/2023]

# **Junior Web Developer**

**Tickbird** https://tickbird.com/

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania Responsibilities

- working in a team of 8 10 people
- developed the company website interface
- estimate the website features
- code review
- · bug fixes

#### Tech stack:

- Angular
- Figma
- Bootstrap
- Bitbucket
- lira
- Visual Studio Code
- AOS

# [ 16/08/2021 – 16/08/2022 ] **Junior Front-End Web Developer**

#### Frozennlogic SRL

City: Remote

Country: Romania **Responsibilities:** 

- worked in a team of 5 people
- develop reusable web modules that matches pixel perfect with design

- perform changes requested by clients
- bug fixes
- · adjust project style-guide

#### **Tech stack**

- HubspotCMS
- Visual Studio Code
- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS
- JavaScript
- HubL
- Hubspot database
- Avocode
- Figma
- Bitbucket
- Adobe XD

[ 07/10/2019 - 11/08/2021 ]

# **Senior Account Payable Analyst**

# **Genpact**

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania Responsibilities:

- invoice processing (North America & Canada)
- process improvement
- quality check for teammates
- invoice splitting
- · manual postings
- · handle email enquiries

#### Tools:

- Basware
- SAP
- Coupa
- Microsoft Excel

[ 01/06/2018 - 04/10/2019 ]

# **Account Payable Analyst with German**

#### **Boombarier Transportation**

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania Responsibilities:

- worked in a team of 20 people
- invoice processing (BT Germany)
- part of inter-company process
- owner of intra-company process
- process improvement

#### Tools:

- SAP
- Microsoft Excel

[ 22/02/2017 – 31/05/2018 ] **Scanning Analyst** 

# **Bombardier Transportation**

City: Cluj Napoca Country: Romania **Responsibilities:** 

- sorting paper invoices
- scanning invoices (BT- France, BT- Poland)
- archiving invoices and send it back to site
- back-up for teammates
- process improvement
- Verify (software) manually validate basic information of invoices that failed OCR

# **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

# [ 01/12/2021 – 31/03/2022 ] **Certificate of completion**

Udemy - The Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-web-developer-zero-to-mastery/learn/lecture/ 22648019?start=0#overview

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies: Software and applications development and analysis

Link: https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-64c41f13-7385-461c-972d-6715f90a213b/

# [ 11/2019 - 04/2020 ] **Junior Web Developer**

# The informal School of IT

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

During this course I've learned the basics and syntax of HTML5. CSS3 and JavaScript but also advanced topics like HTML elements, attributes, form elements, CSS box model, flexbox, media gueries, bootstrap, JS Objects, ES6, advanced functions, etc.

I have also learned the ReactJS Architecture that we used to deploy 2 of our projects ("My IMDB" and "My Online CV").

Along with these I learned the GIT principles and basic commands.

[2014 - 2016]

# Masters degree in "Business administration: Trade, Tourism and Services"

### Faculty of Economic Sciences and Business Administration

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

This degree it was an in depth study of everything I learned for bachelor.

[2011 - 2014]

# **Bachelor degree in "Economics: Trade, Tourism and Services"**

# Faculty of Economic Sciences and Business Administration

City: Cluj - Napoca Country: Romania

Marketing (marketing basics, brand marketing, tourism marketing)

- Accounting (bases of accounting, financial accounting)
- Finance (Finance, finance and taxation)
- Tourism (tourism economy, international tourism)
- Service Management

# **PORTFOLIO**

#### **Projects**

My main personal projects are:

- https://la-luca.web.app/
- https://vasiluca32.github.io/My-Online-CV/
- https://vasiluca32.github.io/Robofriends/
- https://vasiluca32.github.io/Recipes/

You can find all of the personal projects I have worked on below.

https://luca-vasile-portfolio.netlify.app/

Also you may check my GitHub profile as well:

https://github.com/vasiluca32?tab=repositories

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Romanian

Other language(s):

# **English**

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING B2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

# **IOB-RELATED SKILLS**

## [Current] Job-related skills

The skill that found most important since I starded working in the IT field is the countinuous learning if it can be said like that or the discipline that leads to it because different companies will use different technologies and so, the Web Development field is in constant evolution.

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

React Js | Angular | Firebase | GIT (GitHub) | VS Code | HTML | CSS | SCSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | Sublime Text 3 | Git Bash | NextJS | Flgma | Avocode | Atlassian Confluence and Iira | HubSpot CMS | Hubl | Microsoft Office | Atlassian (JIRA/CONFLUENCE)

# **COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS**

# **Soft Skills**

- Ability to multitask
- Attention to detail
- · Open to new challenges
- Team player
- Creativity
- Problem solving
- High level of flexibility
- Good administration

# **DRIVING LICENCE**

Motorbikes: A В Cars:

# **HOBBIES AND IN-TERESTS**

#### **Hobbies**

I like programing and fitness. Living in the countryside I enjoy long walks through the forest with my dogs. I'm a huge Formula 1 and MotoGP fan and I always make sure to not miss any race. When time allows, I enjoy riding my motorcycle or playing racing video games.